Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The Supervisor, Volume 4, Number 23, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: The Supervisor, Volume 4, Numbr 24, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: The Supervisor, Volume 4, Number 25, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: The Suprvisor, Volume 4, Number 25, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: The Supervosir, Volume, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Sypervisor, Volume 7, Nubmer 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: The Supervisor, Volume 6, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 16, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 15, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number, 14, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: the Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 13, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 13, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: The Supervisor, Volume 5, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Louisville, Kentucky. Item is in English.
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: The Postal Supervisor, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 13, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 14, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 15, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 7, Number 16, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, volume 8, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 8, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: The Suprvisor, Volume 9, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 9, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 9, No 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 9, No 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 9, No 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: The Suprvisor, Volume 12, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Numbr 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 13, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Box 38, Folder (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor, Volume 10, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 2, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 3, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 4, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 5, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 6, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: The Supervisor, volume 11, Number 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: The Supervisor, Volume 11, Number 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: The Supervisor, Volume 12, Number 1, Publication (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Box 39, Folder (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the United Electrical Radio & Maching Workers of America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Grievance Procedure as Amended September 16, 1942, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Job Analysis Work Sheet, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Notes on Sickness Absenteeism, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Personnel Selection During Conversion from Civilian Production to War Production, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Plant Emergency Defense Organization, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Suggestion Plan to Increase War Production, 1942, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: What Keeps Employees Away From Work?, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Safety Rules for Individual Jobs, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Changes in Terms of Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-CIO Covering Production and Maintenance Employes, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: rehabilitation of Employes Returning from Military Service, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Policies and Procedures for the Administration of Pontiac Moto Division Rehabilitation Program for Employees Returning from Military Service, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: General Motors Corporation's Position on Union Demand for Sick Bonus, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Organization and funcion of Women's Personnel Section, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Job Evaluation Manual, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Enter Pontiac Suggestion Plan Now!, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Box 39, Folder (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Plan of Representation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Industrial representation Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: You and Your Job in General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Hospital and Surgical Care Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Looking Ahead, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: General Motors Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Employees' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Work Safety!, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: A Message to our Employees on the Employment and Defense Problem, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Man to Man on the Job, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Fire Prevention, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: A Story of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Your Job With Cadillac, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Producing More for Victory, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Records of Employees, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: How a Nation Gets Strong, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: What General Motors has Learned About Training Men, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    By R.G. French. Item is in English.
- Box 39, Folder (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Outline of Functions on Education and Training Department, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Labor Relations in General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Fisher Body Division, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Personnel Testing and Research Department, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Employee Service Recognition, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: How Division Conduct Management Meetings, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Cadillac Craftsman, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Pulling Together, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: On the Job at Moraine Products, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Statement of Motors Position on Unionization of Foremen, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Safety in General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: New Departure, Personnel Department, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: The Organization of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Your Key to opportunity, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: The Worker Speaks, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Awards for Good Ideas, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Ideas Pay Off, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Body by Fishers, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: GM and its American Indutrial Team, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Helping Dealers Make More and Better Friends, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Local Wage Agreement Between GMC Truck & Coach Division, General Motors Corporation and Local 594 UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Local Agreement Between Detroit Diesel Engine Division and the UAW-CIO Shop Committee, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Facts about General Motors Profits, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Local Wage Agreement Between AC Spark Plug Division and Local No. 651 U.A.W - C.I.O, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: You and Your Job, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Wage Agreement Between Harrison Radiator Divisio and G.M Unit No. 1, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Story of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Handbook for Employees, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Serving Our Employees Through the Personnel Department, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Local Wage Agreement Between AC Spart plug Division and Local No. 651, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Where Each Dollar Went, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: GM Corporaion Newsletter, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Development Program for Stenographers, Typists & Clerks, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Why Cadillac Operates a Suggestion System, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
    By J. M. Roche. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Grievance Procedure, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Seniority Agreement Between New Departure Division and the UAW-CIO Local 626, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Seniority Agreement Between Harrison Radiator Division, General Motors Corporation and G. M. Unit No. 1, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: For Your Protection, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Box 39, Folder (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Development and Growth of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Harlow Curtice. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Personnel Function and its Benefits to Plant Management, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Your GM Savings-Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Your GM Savings - Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: General Motors Savings - Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: AC Sales Inventory and Examiner's Manual, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Statistical Methods in Quality Control, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Principles of Creative Activity, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Supplemental Agreement Covering Supplemental Unemploymens Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Supplemental Agreements Covering Pension Plan Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Local Agreements between AC Spark Plug Division and Local 651, UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the Pattern Makers' League of North America, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Supplemental Agreement Covering Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Local Agreements Between Buick Motor Division and Local 599 UAW, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Supplemental Agreement covering Pension Plan and Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Supplemental Agreement Covering Pension Plan and Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Supplemental Agreement Covering Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Work and Work Standards at Buick, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: A Look at the Buick Supervisor's Safety Job, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Local Wage Agreements Between AC Spark Plug Division and Local 651, UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Supplemental Agreements Covering Pension Plan and Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Designed for General Motors Salaried Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Your Inurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Designed for General Motors ourly-Rate Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Designed for General Motor Hourly-Rate Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: 1955 Press Conference, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: A Look at GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: How the Sub Plan Will Apply at GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Your Extra Benefits, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: How GM Operates Without UAW Pact, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Detroit, Michigan. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Delco Radio Broadcaster, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Supplemental Agreement to National Agreement, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: To The Men and Women of General Motors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Information Bulletin for GM Editors, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Previews of GM Posters, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Summary of Service Recognition Plans, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Previews of posters, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 41: Tuning in Delco Radio Division, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Ten Years of industrial Peace at GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: I'm with GM, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: General Motors retirement Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Your GM Pension, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Reply of General Motors President to President of UAW, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)